http://www.worldatwork.org/privacy-policy/

WorldatWork Online Privacy Policy
Information WorldatWork Collects About You
WorldatWork collects information about you when you establish an account or place an order for products or services. Information also is collected when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback and download content or participate in online webinars. Website use information is collected using cookies.
WorldatWork’s website uses various forms and methods to make it convenient for you to request information, order publications, register for seminars or events, chat or post messages, or for us to contact you. This requires that you provide contact information, including your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number and/or credit card information.
Each time you visit the WorldatWork website, our web server automatically recognizes your domain name, not your email address. Aggregate information is collected on the pages you access and information you volunteer, such as site registrations. This information is used for internal review and improving the content of our webpages.
Cookies
Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.
For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org.
You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, some WorldatWork website features may not function as a result.
How WorldatWork Will Use Your Information
WorldatWork collects information to process any orders you make, manage your account and, if you agree, to email, phone or contact you by mail or fax about our organization and its products and services.
WorldatWork uses your information collected from the website to personalize your repeat visits to the website.
Using Online Community Discussions and Online Surveys
When participating in Online Community discussions, users are asked to review and abide by rules and etiquette points. By participating in the Online Community discussions, you consent to share certain personal data (including user name). Each WorldatWork member’s email address in the Online Community is a "blind" address, thus concealing the email address but still allowing messages to be sent. The Online Community message volume and the content of messages may be monitored to ensure proper use.
WorldatWork also surveys members and customers on key research topics affecting the profession and the field. All online survey data is reported in aggregate. No individual company data ever is released, identified or shared with survey partner companies. Unique survey identifiers (e.g., member identification number) are kept confidential and only used by authorized WorldatWork staff to contact with survey participants, if necessary. WorldatWork will ask for your consent to survey you; you can refuse to participate in that survey by not providing consent.
Where and How Long WorldatWork Holds Information About You
You are a customer and/or a member who has achieved a designation certification or is a Lifetime Member.
WorldatWork holds all relevant data required to verify designation or lifetime membership. This is housed indefinitely within our business’s database located in Phoenix, Ariz., USA.
This information will be used for all required verification purposes and, if you have given consent, for outreach by WorldatWork on new products and services, or any appropriate vendors and partners of WorldatWork for the same.
You are a customer who has made a purchase through WorldatWork.
WorldatWork holds all relevant data required to verify designation, consumer purchase history or any historical data required by governing laws and regulations, including tax and contracts laws. These are housed for 8 years within our business’s database located in Phoenix, Ariz., USA.
This information will be used for all required verification purposes and required fulfillment of contracts and, if you have given consent, for outreach by WorldatWork on new products and services, or any appropriate vendors and partners of WorldatWork for the same.
After 8 years, if no additional account activity has occurred, all identifiable data will be removed from WorldatWork databases.
You are a customer who has downloaded content or registered to view free online content but have not made a purchase.
WorldatWork holds all relevant data required to verify designation, consumer download history or any historical data required for standard business practices. This will be housed for 3 years within our business’s database located in Phoenix, Ariz., USA.
This information will be used for all required verification purposes and, if you have given consent, for outreach by WorldatWork, or any appropriate vendors and partners of WorldatWork for the same.
At 3 years, if no additional account activity has occurred, all identifiable data will be removed from WorldatWork databases.
You have created a customer account with no additional activity.
WorldatWork holds all relevant data required to verify designation, potential purchases, consumer download history or any historical data required for standard business practices. This will be housed for 1 year within our business’s database located in Phoenix, Ariz., USA.
This information will be used for all required verification purposes and, if you have given consent, for outreach by WorldatWork, or any appropriate vendors or partners of WorldatWork.
At 1 year, if no additional account activity has occurred, all identifiable data will be removed from WorldatWork databases.
How WorldatWork Shares Information and Your Choices and Preferences
WorldatWork will engage and contract with third-party companies (e.g., service providers) to provide services that help us with our business activities, such as cloud hosting services. These third-party service providers are limited to only using information as instructed to provide contracted services to WorldatWork.
If you have given consent, we will pass your personal information to our vendors and partners so that they may offer you their products and services. For example, WorldatWork may share your personal information with exhibitors and sponsors of a WorldatWork conference, webinar or other similar event that you attend. WorldatWork will not share your information for marketing purposes with companies outside the WorldatWork network of partners and vendors.
In processing your order, we may send your details to and use information from credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies.
Marketing
WorldatWork will send you information about products and services of ours and other related partner or vendor companies that may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date. At any time, you have the right to stop WorldatWork from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your information to our vendors or partners. If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please click here.
WorldatWork also will disclose your personal information
As required by law to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process. To the extent WorldatWork is legally permitted to do so, we will take commercially reasonable steps to notify you in the event that we are required to provide your personal information to third parties as part of a legal process. WorldatWork also may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including requests from national security or law enforcement authorities.
When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a written government request.
If WorldatWork becomes involved in a merger, acquisition or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure that the acquiring organization agrees to protect your personal information in accordance with the commitments we have made in this Privacy Policy and that the acquiring organization will provide notice before personal information, customer information or business information becomes subject to a different privacy notice.
To any other third party as described in this section of the policy and earlier in the “Marketing” section of this policy with your prior consent to do so.
WorldatWork will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. We do not otherwise sell your personal information to third parties.
WorldatWork uses email addresses for its own purposes of keeping members and customers informed about association events and providing product, service and information announcements. In addition, if you have consented to receive email from vendor and partner companies of WorldatWork, you will receive periodic messages from WorldatWork Local Network partner associations, research partners, vendors and consulting partners. We offer you the opportunity to regulate the type of email communications you receive from us by modifying your preferences.
You can change your preferences at any time. Go to My Profile (you must be logged in) and select "Edit Info" under your name in the left navigation. You may change your preferences on your Account Information page. If you have any questions or comments, email customerexperience@worldatwork.org, or call 877-951-9191 (United States or Canada) or 480-951-9191 (other countries).
If you supply WorldatWork with your postal address, you will receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products, services and upcoming events. You also may receive periodic mailings from other reputable companies; however, you can put your name on our do-not-share list. If you do not wish to receive other mailings, please let us know by
e-mailing customerexperience@worldatwork.org;
calling 877-951-9191 (United States or Canada) or 480-951-9191 (other countries); or
checking the appropriate box on the data request form when making the request.
If you supply WorldatWork with your telephone number, you will only receive telephone contact from us. We do not share telephone numbers with other companies for any purpose.
Access and Correct Your Information
You have the right to request a copy of the information that WorldatWork holds about you. Also, WorldatWork wants to ensure your personal information is accurate and current. You may ask us to correct inaccurate information or remove information.
Upon request we will provide you with access to your personal data. WorldatWork will make commercially reasonable efforts to provide you reasonable access to any of your personal or other account information we maintain within 30 days of your access request. If we cannot honor your request within the 30-day period, we will tell you when we will be able to provide access. In the unlikely event that we cannot provide you access to your information, we will explain why we cannot do so.
If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email customerexperience@worldatwork.org or call 877-951-9191 (United States or Canada) or 480-951-9191 (other countries). WorldatWork will provide you a form to fill out to request access to your information. There may be a nominal charge for this service.
How WorldatWork Keeps Information Secure
WorldatWork uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving member and nonmember data exchanged with our site. Appropriate security measures are in place at our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you.
WorldatWork follows and is compliant with Payment Card Industry (PCI) Data Security standards to protect you while you shop at worldatwork.org. WorldatWork uses the industry standard in secure server software. All of your personal information, including your credit card number and course transcripts, is encrypted before it is sent across the Internet.
Other Websites
Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to the WorldatWork website. When you access other websites, read and review their specific privacy policies.
Changes to WorldatWork’s Privacy Policy
WorldatWork regularly reviews this privacy policy and will place any updates on this webpage. This privacy policy was last updated on May 25, 2018.
WorldatWork reserves the right to change its privacy policy. Any changes to the policy will be posted on this page and will be effective immediately upon posting. We also will post a notice that this Privacy policy has changed. By using our website, you acknowledge that you agree to the WorldatWork Privacy Policy Statement. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site.
Contact Us
If you have questions about our privacy policy,  contact WorldatWork’s Customer Relationship Services team, 877-951-9191 (United States or Canada) or + 480-951-9191 (other countries), customerexperience@worldatwork.org or write WorldatWork, 14040 N. Northsight Blvd., Scottsdale, AZ, USA, 85260.
Select Category
Certification
Community
Education
Events
Public Policy
Resources
Have Questions?
